Si "Leo" Wang

leo.wang142001@gmail.com
Cell: 289-894-3837
github.com/asi4n-inv4sion
linkedin.com/in/leo-wang-955982193

Skills

Strong teamwork, leadership, and communication skills developed through 5 years as a member of the Royal Canadian Air Cadets.

Exceptional independent working, time-management, and organizational skills displayed through academics and extracurricular activities.

Competent in the base structure of programming in Python3 and C learned through three academic courses, and numerous personal projects.

Certified in CPR-C and National Lifeguard by the Lifesaving Society

Education

Sep 2019 - Present

University of Toronto

- Pursuing a B.Sc of Computer Science, specialization in Software Engineering.
- Received a renewable entrance scholarship of \$3 000 for outstanding academic performance in Grade 12 (average of 95%+).

Projects

Mar - Jun 2019

Python Graphing Calculator – Grade 12 Final Project

- Successfully created a functioning graphing calculator using the PyGame module.
- Created a function to solve the issue of floating-point number multiplication and division being inaccurate.
- Actively communicated and developed alongside a classmate using GitHub.

Apr 2020 - Present

Python Discord Bot

- Developing a bot for personal use among friends.
- Current notable features: a server command that allows any user to search the WolframAlpha database directly from a discord server, and a election system with file IO to keep track of candidates and voters.

Experience

Sep 2016 - Apr 2019

Aurora United Church - Volunteer

- Setup, serve, and tear down a community breakfast one Saturday morning per month from 8:00am to 12:00pm.
- Kept a healthy relationship with the community and the volunteers to ensure a smooth functioning kitchen and meal was being served.

Extracurricular Activities

2013 - 2019

Air Cadets

- Held the position of Squadron Training Warrant Officer and flight commander of flight 3.
 - Responsibilities included planning the training plan for the 2018-2019 year, teach classes of cadets, and upholding squadron standards.
- Developed leadership and teamwork skills through years of training and leading private or public activities.

Sep - Apr 2019

FIRST Robotics Team

- Core programmer and engineer for our high school's first robotics team.
- Helped conceptualize a solution to a set of problems given to by the FIRST Robotics Competition.
 - Attended many seminars and quick builds to quickly learn how the competition works and how to create and design a functioning robot for the competition.
- Received the Rookie All-Star award at the 2019 FIRST Robotics Competition.

Oct 2009 - Present

Instrumental Music

- Played piano for 10+ years, finished RCM practical level 10 in May 2019. Still continuing to play in the present, learning new works individually.
- Played alto saxophone for 4+ years, mainly for high school bands and one term in the
 UofT concert band. Still continuing to play in the present, learning new works individually.